Guide to the Associated Actors and Artistes of America Records WAG.110
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Affiliates, 1909-1993; 11681
  - Subseries VII:B: American Guild of Variety Artists (AGVA), 11682
    - AGVA, Local Convention Nominations, New Jersey-Youngstown, 1947; 11712 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - AGVA, Litigation Fees, 1948-1950; 11711 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - AGVA, Litigation Fees, 1951-1957; 11710 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - AGVA, Conference Proceedings, 1942; 11709 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - AGVA, Member Petitions, 1946; 11708 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - AGVA, Four A's Executive Committee, 1947-1948; 11707 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - AGVA, Background for Congressional Inquiry, 1948; 11706 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - AGVA, Clipping File, 1947-1948; 11705 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - AGVA, Continued Litigation, 1948-1951; 11704 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - AGVA: National Leadership Crisis: Background and Evidence, 1968-1969; 11703 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - AGVA, Background and Evidence, 1970-1971; 11702 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - AGVA, Background and Evidence, Jan-Jun 1972, 11701 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - AGVA, Background and Evidence, Jul-Dec 1972, 11700 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - AGVA, Background and Evidence, 1973; 11699 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - AGVA, Background and Evidence, Jan-Mar 1974, 11698 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - AGVA, Background and Evidence, April 1974-1975, 11697 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - AGVA, Member Correspondence, 1968-1971; 11696 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - AGVA, Member Correspondence, 1972-1974; 11695 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - AGVA, Roberts and Miller Reports, 1972; 11694 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - AGVA, Clipping File and Basic Agreements, 1968-1976; 11693 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - AGVA, VEGA Dispute, 1975-1976; 11692 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - AGVA, Finance Memos, 1972-1974; 11691 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - AGVA, Alan Cory Litigation, 1978-1979; 11690 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - AGVA, Penny Singleton Charges, 1959-1963; 11689 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - AGVA, Richard Jones Charges, 1950, 1958-1968; 11688 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - AGVA: National Leadership Crisis: Minutes, Special Four A's Meeting, Feb 1972, 11687 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - AGVA: Senate Committee Hearings, 1962; 11686 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - AGVA: House Committee Hearings, 1948, Vols 1-2, 11685 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - AGVA: House Committee Hearings, 1948, Vols 3-4, 11684 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - AGVA, House Committee Hearings, 1948, Vols 5-6, 11683 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Series VIII: Unprocessed Materials, 1919-2014; 438134
  Comprised mainly materials related to disputes between various entertainment groups and the decisions of the International Board, as well as the correspondence of Frederick O'Neal, president of the Actors' Equity Association from 1964 to 1973. This series also contains historical documents from the union's early history.
  This series has not been arranged by an archivist; original order of these materials is unknown.
  - American Guild of Variety Artists Correspondence, Membership Information, and Meeting Notes; Agreements; Complaints; Organizing Materials; and Donations and Contributions., 1919-1992; 438137 (Box 12)
  - Asociacion Puertorriquena de Artistas y Tecnicos del Espectaculo (APATE) and Appeals Made to International Board., 1939-1991; 438138 (Box 13)
  - Immigration and Naturalization Agency; Screen Extras Guild Correspondence and Grievances; and Industrial Relations Research Association Papers., 1930-1991; 438142 (Box 14)
  - Italian Actors Union Minutes, Correspondence, Constitution, and Election Materials; Interchangeability Agreements; Screen Extras Guild Grievances and 1980 Election Complaints; Screen Actors Guild Robert Cleaves Hearing (with Cassette Tape); and Reports and Convention Materials., 1921-1999; 438145 (Box 15)
  - Film When Wallace Got the Vote; Jurisdiction Committee Reports and Other Documents; and Organizing Materials., 1947-1984; 438149 (Box 16)
  - President's Reports; Frederick O'Neal Biographical Information, Correspondence, and Memorialization; and the American National Theatre and Academy Re-Organizing Correspondence and Materials., 1920-1993; 438162 (Box 17)
  - Entertainment and Ball (1940) Fundraising and Other Materials; National Entertainment Industry Council and American Guild of Variety Artists Conference Minutes and Correspondence; and International Board Decisions on Disputes Between Various Entertainment Unions., 1938-1957; 438168 (Box 18)
  - International Board Decisions on Disputes Between Various Entertainment Unions and Frederick O'Neal Actors' Equity Association Correspondence., 1937-1971; 438171 (Box 19)
  - Frederick O'Neal Correspondence (Personal and Actors' Equity Association)., 1965-1979; 438173 (Box 20)
  - International Board Agendas and Frederick O'Neal Correspondence (Emphasis on Racial Equality Issues Outside of and Relating to Actors' Equity Association)., 1959-1981; 438174 (Box 21)
  - Member Photograph, Mae Williams Postcard, and 1974 Charter, 1974, undated; 464484 (Box A001)
  - 2 wood plaques,one awarded to the 4 A's in 1976, and the other to Theodore Bikel, the Union's President, in 1999; 2 certificates, both the ""Award of Patriotism"" to the 4 A's in 1985 and 1987; 1 plastic sign of the 4 A's logo; 3 photographs of Theodore Bikel: 1 black and white of him by himself, and 2 color of him with Presidents Bush and Clinton. These last two are accompanied by letters; 4 color photographs with captions of the AFL-CIO Executive Council, from 1971, 1979, 1981 and 1986., 590757 (Box 22)
  - 2014 Accretion: Report on Consolidation, 1940; 2014.145; 593092 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - 2014 Accretion: Constitution, 1992; 593120 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 2014 Accretion: Historical Documents, 1910-1993; 593121 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - 2014 Accretion: Correspondence with Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, 1983-2001; 593122 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - 2014 Accretion: Correspondence, 1919-2014; 593123 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - 2014 Accretion: Clippings, 1989-2004; 593124 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - 2014 Accretion: Per Capita Negotiations, 1932-1994; 2014.162; 593093 (Box 23, Folder 7-10, Box 24, Folder 1)
  - 2014 Accretion: Per Capita Special Assessment, 1997-2010; 593125 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 2014 Accretion: Per Capita State Affiliations, 1990-1996; 593126 (Box 24, Folder 3)